hello Peter I took the truck for a test
drive today and I lasted about a quarter
of a mile just I could hear pinging and
detonation sounding you know indicating
gasoline was getting into the system I
went ahead and uh brought it back to the
shop and you'll see the video I wanted
to let you know that the tubes were
exposed when I got back as you see and
also that there was a 1.5v d Cel battery
attached to the cell during the test
drive so hopefully uh these are okay for
you to observe and maybe give me some
feedback on that and uh wait to hear
from you thank
you hey Peter this is what it looked
like after I came back from the drive
the uh plates are
exposed and it was bubbling like this
when I took it off
with uh right now I do have power to it
but when I first got back I took top off
and it was bubbling like this I was just
curious is this what the damn thing is
supposed to look like I know looking at
Alex's video he has a Cell It's supposed
to be in stage three that bubbles and
does gooey stuff like
this anyway I want to get uh see this so
you got a take on it and I also uh did a
modification
I don't know if you can see that I got
wood spacers all the way around it it's
totally isolated by the wood small wood